In the last three weeks of February, we've shipped more code
than almost all of September and October combined.
So how do we increase our velocity so much
and how do we maintain quality.
Hi, everyone.
So this is actually my first, proper talk at an event like this.
So, bear with me if I trip over my list.
The talk that I'm going to be giving
today is just about how I've actually stopped handwriting code.
And I'm actually not the only one either.
So I stopped writing code by hand
in about September of 2025.
And it's not just me.
Every single one of our engineers has actually completely
restructured their code development workflows to be more AI native.
And then as a result, developer velocity has significantly increased.
And I'm going to go into some of these things.
But before I start just a quick show of hands, who uses coding agents
like every single day in their like, code workflows, right?
You open up your laptop,
you have the coding agent there, and you're executing on tasks.
Yeah. Fantastic. Okay, good.
Hopefully you guys will get something out of this. And,
we have a lot of coding agents, right?
There's a bunch of different types of coding agents.
And I mentioned earlier
that we've all restructured and become a lot more AI native.
When someone says something like that to me, my first question is,
what the heck does it mean to be a AI native?
And second, what were the outcomes, right?
Like what actually happened?
What were the results?
And so I mentioned earlier that I developer velocity has increased
significantly.
So developer velocity is notoriously difficult to measure.
Right.
But a simple definition that I think generally people can agree on
is that we're asking how quickly can we reliably turn ideas
into working software, right.
How reliably can we do that?
And so there are a few signals
that we kind of now rely on to figure out whether those things happen.
And it doesn't need to be perfect.
But if you keep these things in mind and you use the same measures
across the time span, you can get an idea that, hey, something is changing,
something is improving, something might not be working as well.
So one of them is deployment frequency.
So how often do we ship changes to production?
For us
this works with number of commits because we deploy on a continuous timeline.
So we deploy every single day on almost every commit.
What does that change? Failure rate. Right.
Like what percentage of those changes and the closing incidents.
And someone gets paged on call.
And then that needs to be rolled back.
And what are the lead times for our changes?
So how long does it take for us to go from being open to being merged?
And how long do our issues, you know, like issue management system
in our case, Linear?
How long do they stay in progress until they get moved to done?
So again, they don't need to be perfect.
But if you use the same measures across a period of time,
you'll get an indication that something has changed or hasn't changed.
So this is a
commit graph over the last six months.
That's yeah, that's our actual commit graph over the last six months.
In the last three weeks of February, we've shipped more code
than almost all of September and October combined.
And that's while we've been doing that.
Our change failure rate has stayed pretty much consistent,
and it's even decreased a little bit in February.
Same with our lead times.
For our peers, we're trending down, which means we're merging code a lot faster.
And then the same thing with our linear issues
where they're staying in the in-progress state a lot less,
headcount hasn't changed much in those last few weeks.
Right.
And you'll notice also there's the P50 and the P90 five times.
There are some linear tickets that really mess up this, this data.
So how do we increase
our velocity so much and how do we maintain quality.
Right.
The change failure rate is a good measure of as we increase
our velocity, does that quality decrease or get messed up.
So let me introduce you to some tools just to give you
a bit of an overview on what I'm using every single day.
And I'll take you through a workflow that essentially works for me.
So you've got your main coding agents, you have Claude
Codex, you have this interesting tool in the middle here called conductor.
How many people have heard of conductor?
Oh, okay. Interesting. Cool.
We have cursor, which also actually is a creating agent,
but is also an ID.
And then any sort of anything you can use to use a terminal, I use warp.
In this case it doesn't really matter.
I'll go through how these play into the workflow a little bit more later.
So let's talk about the actual workflow
that makes this AI native right?
As an engineer, when someone gives you a task
or an issue or a problem, how do you usually start right?
You start with a plan.
Some way of gathering context, gathering information,
and then you come up with an idea of a solution that you want to work on.
So you then review that plan, right.
You might give it to a colleague, you might give it to someone else,
or you review it yourself to see if it makes sense.
If it meets the the requirements that you've met and then you execute, right.
You write your code, you will make the changes
that you need to make, and then you review it again.
Right? You give it to someone else. You give it to one of your colleagues.
You get someone to review those changes, and then you ship and then you review.
So there's a lot of reviewing that happens,
and there's a lot of changes and plans and things that you're doing in between.
So what's interesting about this new workflow or the way
a new way of working is that
these stages, the planning,
the execute stages are largely automated by coding agents.
I, as the engineer,
actually focus a lot more, and a lot heavily on the review stages.
And so what does that actually look like in practice?
Right.
If you've got any sort of, coding agent opened up here,
you have a prompt, you give it a prompt, but you're in the plan mode initially.
Right.
So something that I really recommend for everyone is that if you're making
big, complex changes, it's really, really beneficial to start in plan mode.
You kind of want to work with your agent just as you were working with one of
your colleagues, where you're spending time exploring the code base,
discovering what needs to change and why.
So you give the agent a clear and concise prompt,
and you treat the agent's response like a mini design doc
that you would review, just as you would
any other design doc that you received from your team.
You're right.
You need to review the plan that ends up.
You look at the structure. Does it make sense?
Will it meet your requirements, all that sort of stuff.
So this is the best part about the planning stage
that you can go back and forth with the agent.
And another really important thing is it's a great time to intervene.
Intervene early right.
Think about plans that you create as tech designs and then you implement them.
And then someone's like, hey, why did we plan it this way?
We should have just done something differently.
And now you have to change your entire implementation.
This the same principle here.
Nothing really changes.
So the next thing is you execute.
But the tip here is that you execute with a fresh context window.
And so why does this actually help.
Why what what benefit does it provide here.
Right.
Context.
Your context window is really important because if you start loading things up
with things that you don't need,
the agent finds it more difficult to figure out what's actually relevant.
Right?
Your agent is focussed on what it needs to do,
but if it has a bunch of information that's irrelevant.
It's going to make.
It's going to be much more likely to make mistakes.
But this is where usually most people will find the issues
with coding agents, right? They're going to write broken code.
They're going to get stuck.
They don't really know how to fix the issues that they face.
And so this is where I want to introduce probably the most important concept of
this talk. And that's feedback loops.
So if the workflow is like
the skeleton, the feedback loops are like the nervous system.
They give you away or they give the agent a way to actually
react to things that are happening.
Feedback loops give your agent a way to verify their own work,
and the better your feedback loops, the more likely it is for your agent
to actually give you a working output that meets your requirements.
Some examples of feedback loops that you probably already
have in your repositories. By the way.
Running tests through the CLI
type checking, linting, formatting a new one that looks a bit new
but actually already exists and has existed for a while,
but it's browser access, so you have your end to end tests that you run.
Sometimes through the CLI,
but this is just another interface for your agent to be able to then access
the browser and get information in context on what's happening.
You have your system logs, so information that might exist somewhere
in like some log file, in a Docker container somewhere that,
you can read through and exist and you read through yourself,
but you might want to give the agent a way to read through those log files as well.
And then you have, again, a relatively new concept, but MCP servers
that essentially allow your agent to communicate with external systems
in a more structured way.
So how does your agent
actually know that those feedback loops are available?
So I'm sure everyone that works with agents have an idea that you have
these things called like agent or MD
files, claude.md files, things like that right there.
Files that are always
added to your conversations with your agents.
So you might have a cloud file or an agent, somebody file at the start
of every single new thread that you have with your agent,
that all the information, that file gets added into your thread.
And so the agent always knows that the things in that file exist
and there and can refer back to them.
So you don't have to retell it over and over again.
And so this is one of those situations where your feedback loops
what feedback loops are available.
How do you invoke them.
And then when do you invoke them.
That's really important stuff to put in your agent.
So MD file so your agent can go back and refer to those things when you need to.
He's like a snippet of our agent.
So MD5 I'm
not sure if that's readable everywhere, but it's really, really straightforward.
We just tell it that, hey you can run install using but install
you can run test using run tests, you can run lint, you can run a specific
test file using bug test and then the path to the test file.
So it's things like this.
And that can get a little bit more complicated.
But what and if you set this up properly by the way,
you'll notice that at the end of your agent's work
you'll see a bunch of linting steps, testing steps, and ways
to verify that the code that been produced actually works.
And actually runs at the minimum. And so
what's
interesting here is that this works great for simple workflows,
things that are almost kind of like self documented, or things that might be
a little bit more complicated that isn't already documented in your code.
But if you start adding complex workflows to this file,
you'll notice that things will start getting ignored, right?
Parts of your agent.
So MD file will not always be relevant at all times.
And so the more complex, the more complexity you add to this,
the less important each individual unit of information becomes.
And so this is where I'm introducing, I guess the next concept
that I want to talk about, which is agent skills.
I'm sure a bunch of who's used or heard of,
agent skills so far in this room.
Okay. Awesome.
So some people have, so I'll give you a rundown on what agent skills are.
So if normal documentation,
markdown files that you have in your code base explain what something is.
An agent skill is a way to explain how to do something step
by step for the agent, so you can think of them as procedural guides
that give you agent new capabilities
and so one interesting thing that is unlocked with agent skills is that
you also give the agent information on when to invoke that skill.
Right? You don't just tell it what to do.
You also tell it when it's applicable.
And the agent can then figure out when you're doing something naturally
that, hey, this skill is applicable to what we're doing
right now, I'm going to grab the context from that skill
so it's lazy loaded information in your agent context.
Some examples of interesting skills that we have.
You can see these on the Tessl registry.
You have like a, a systematic debugging skill that teaches your agent
how to actually approach a bug step by step.
You might be facing a bug that's specific to your info, right?
And debugging that might not be very obvious.
So you might give the agent a step by step workflow on which APIs
you need to call to figure out if there's a problem in a specific space.
Another one is building an MCP, so you might have a bunch of small services
that you might want to start repeatedly updating to have an MCP.
So before you can package that up into a step by step workflow that now
the agent can use to then extract each of those new services
into its own MCP server.
So instead of the agent improvising every single time,
or you having to give it information or the same prompt every single time,
you can just give it this repeatable playbook
that makes the behaviour much more reliable.
And it's also a feedback loop that you can control.
So there are two skills that I use
in almost every single workflow that I do every day.
That's a code review skill and a simplified skill.
So I'll quickly skim through these.
But the code review skill is essentially run.
I run it at the end of every single coding thread that I have, right?
I work with the agent, I do a bunch of work, I read the changes,
and then I run the review skill again in a fresh context window,
and it will run a review on your code, just like it would with
any other engineers that you have.
Where it will try to identify issues with your style,
it will identify architectural concerns.
You might identify some bugs or some code smells that you've added,
and it'll produce a report that you can then figure out how you want to action.
Right. It's not going to action it for you.
It's just creating a report.
And then you can decide whether, hey, this part of it makes sense.
This part doesn't. I'm going to figure out whether I want to action this or not.
Another one that has been
incredibly useful for me has been the code simplify skill, right?
So agents often produce a lot of code, and that code isn't always very useful.
Right?
The code might be too bloated.
It might have unnecessary duplication.
It might have more
ways of doing something than actually needs to be done.
And it also might have recreated concepts that already exist in your code base.
So the code simplify skill is a great way of preserving behaviour,
but trying to simplify and lessen the number of lines of code
that you've added.
Because remember, every line of code
that you add to your code base is a liability, right?
It's something that you're going to need to maintain.
It's something that you're gonna need to test and make sure that
either you or your coding agent have context over in the future.
And so if you do this, you'll get some output.
And it says that, hey, like, I've been able to simplify
a bunch of things that you did in your, in your, you know, branch, right?
I can clean up a lot of this stuff.
So I think most of the stuff that I've kind of outlined here,
I think some people have an idea on or is pretty intuitive,
but it's the next part
that gets really, really interesting because we have this workflow,
but it doesn't feel very fast, right?
It doesn't really explain how we went from shipping, like, you know, a few hundred
commits a month to 300 in a week, right?
So this is where the idea of Parallelisation comes in.
So right now a workflow is pretty serial, right?
We plan, we wait for the agent, we review, we wait for the agent,
we PR review, we wait for the agent, and then we deploy it.
Right. So there's a lot of waiting between steps.
And that's the new bottleneck.
Now if you can figure out that initial
workflow
then parallelising it becomes really, really powerful.
But what does that actually look like?
So let me introduce you to conductor.
Conductor uses git work trees to parallelise recruiting agents.
And so for me, I didn't actually know what work trees were until earlier last year.
A lecture is just another check out of the same repo,
sharing the same history on the same machine.
So it essentially means that you can create multiple branches
and work on those branches in parallel on the same machine.
And so something that's really powerful about this is that it's
think of it as you get cloning your repository
again for every feature that you work on for every branch.
But instead of having to do that yourself every single time, Work Trees
gives you a native way of doing it.
Git already has a built in for you,
so now you can have
agent A that's working on a plan on the first workflow, and while you're
waiting for it to finish its plan, you can kick off a plan for agent B,
and while it's working on its plan and doing its own research,
you can kick off a plan for agency. Right?
And what your work looks like now is that you're moving between each agent,
reviewing the plans, reviewing the diffs, the changes, and then running.
You simplify your review or giving it more direction on what it needs to do right.
If you condense all of this,
you're spending a lot less time waiting for things to happen
and spending a lot more time actually just directing
the different agents in your team on what they need to do.
So what does that look like in conductor, for example?
Right.
I can just hit new workspace.
It does all of this for you.
It handles a lot of the underlying logic for you.
It'll create a new workspace and then conductor will go.
Then make a clone of your repository.
And then it'll attach a creating agent to that client.
You end up with multiple workers
and they all have their own changes, their own in progress.
I've created a PR for that first one, so that one's in review.
So you can get a good overview of what's going on,
all the changes that you're working on.
And so something that comes up here now is that
you've got 3 or 4 different changes or issues that you're working on.
You need to you need to make sure that you're still verifying the yourself right.
You need to go to each branch.
You need to make sure that things are running, are working as expected.
And so if every time you clone a repo and you have to do
a bunch of steps to set up your app, this falls apart anyways.
This doesn't really feel like magic.
It doesn't feel like much because you still have to now
copy a bunch of things over and so you're going to get slowed down.
So we need a way of quickly, a way to quickly start your app
and verify your changes.
So some changes that you can make
is having a single script that essentially runs everything for you.
And just checking that into your repository.
Nothing needs to change.
You just run a single script,
and that script contains the things that you need to do
to actually set up the repo and actually then run your product.
So something interesting here is also a lot of what you'll notice
is that for a running instance of your product on your machine,
you might have specific ports that are assigned to it.
You might have specific configurations that are assigned to it.
So you can kind of go two ways.
You can make it possible to have multiple instances of your app
running on the same machine, or you can make it easy to store your app
and then automatically close any other running instances of your app.
It kind of depends, like whatever you whatever works best for your product.
For example, if you're using Next.js or Veet or whatever it is,
it can automatically reassign a new port for your for your web app, right?
So you don't have to necessarily worry about closing the old one.
Well, though, you probably want to clean up
a bunch of those, old, old ports that are running.
So I've gone with number two in my case because it works better
for our set up in our repo.
And so for us, we simply have to install dependencies,
copy over the environment
variables, and then run our dev script once we do all of this.
And so you can add all of this,
to conductor as well.
So every time you hit that new workspace
button, conductor can automatically go and run a script for you.
That sets up the things that you need to do.
Call it install, call the run install.
And I've got a little alias that just copies over my environment
variables from just a folder and a file that exists already in my laptop.
And then the other issue is that you might have existing,
processes running on ports already, right?
You can have a really simple script to close all the ports, right?
Find the ports that are relevant to you,
kill them and then restart your development environment.
So all of these things now
make it easier for you to switch between your workspaces.
Hit run just a single command
and then have your app ready to review the changes that you need.
You've just made.
Well, we can
take Parallelisation one step further.
And so I want to introduce the concept of cloud agents.
So the mental model here is that if your local agents are fully interactive
hands on work
where you're like tight in the loop, your cloud agents are essentially
for offloading background tasks and fire and forget jobs
that can become something that you can review later on.
And there's a bunch of different ways of doing this,
and it really does depend on either a the agent that you're using.
So Claude Code has something that's natively built into it
that uses web agents that you can configure.
Or you might have to build it yourself. Right.
It depends on the agent, depends on what you're working on.
But they let you run tasks asynchronously on some remote infrastructure
somewhere else.
You'll open up or spin up some container.
It'll pull down your repository,
and then it'll run cloud code just as it was on your computer.
Make the changes and then create a PR for you.
So an example of something where this becomes really powerful is
these can start integrating into your slack or into your messaging
systems and platforms and exactly into where you work.
Right. So
it's powerful because oh sorry.
Another example here is that someone pointed out a really small issue
on our registry page, where the skills are being filtered in some way,
and so we had a discussion about it.
We gathered some context,
and then I'm like, hey Claude, can you just look into this for me?
There's no extra like there's no extra fancy stuff that's happened here.
Claude will now go and pull down, on a repo.
It'll make the changes, make the fixes, and then I can go and review
the PR afterwards.
Right.
I don't I don't have to set up the environment locally.
I don't have to do anything now.
I can go and review those code changes later on.
So it's feedback loops, right?
The only reason that works as well as it does is that when Claude goes
and makes those changes, it has a way of not only limiting.
The code, formatting it and figuring out whether what it's done
goes by what you need it to do.
Right? And so it's run the tests.
It's run the other dependencies that it needs to run.
So we fixed up that feedback loop.
And so I know I've just kind of bolted a lot of information there at everyone.
So I'll quickly spend a bit of time to summarise.
I stopped doing the parts of engineering
that agents can do better and faster than me.
And so I can focus on the things that the agents can't do just yet.
And at the moment, that's making decisions and directing the product
under a set of constraints. Right.
That's all where we're working.
We're working under a set of constraints,
and we have to make the decisions because every decision we make ends
up impacting the business as a whole and the direction of the business.
And so it's important to not count that out.
And at the moment are coding.
Agents don't have all the context they need to be able to do that stuff.
And so you can offload some of the things that they can automate.
This is what you do.
So I had used a bunch of concepts.
Those plan mode get work trees, cloud agents, parallelisation,
feedback loops, agent skills, fresh context, a bunch of stuff.
But you notice that these things you already are familiar
with in isolation, right?
These aren't new concepts as a whole.
You already know that when you start a task,
you spend a bit of time planning on how you want to figure it out.
You know that you can parallelise some things that can be parallelised
if they're not going to be overlapping each other.
The feedback loops thing is really important, right?
Have you ever worked in an environment where it takes you a few days
to figure out whether what you've built is actually correct or not?
You know how painful that is to move quickly.
Right.
So this is stuff that we're already familiar with.
And as a result,
it actually applies really, really well to our coding agents as well.
So what
can you actually try in the next 24 to 48 hours that might help
you see some of the improvements that we've made here at Tessl.
So try the plan review and execute workflow.
It's very easy.
You already have your coding agents there for you.
Go into plan mode with have plan.
Make some changes.
Work on the implementation and then execute it in a fresh context
window, right?
Or you can already do that with your existing coding agents.
Number two you'll notice some issues with that.
Make your feedback loop successful and put them in your agent's timed file.
Right. And work on those feedback loops.
The better your feedback loops, the more likely
it is for your agent to actually produce good code.
And I can't overstate that enough.
Everything that we've been doing recently has been improving our feedback loops.
And so the agent can work as autonomously as possible.
And then use conductor. It's a free app.
You just download it and it'll detect your existing clawed code or codex setup.
And you can just run it and it works.
And you'll notice
specifically when you're using conductor and you're using work trees
that how difficult or how easy
it is to actually clone your repo and get somebody else set up on using it.
So another quick question
that I think people are going to be wondering is that we're writing more code.
Is it worse code?
Is it better code?
And we're also producing it a lot faster.
Right.
Well does that going to be degrading our services?
And I answered this question already a little bit earlier.
I velocity went up and I change failure rate went down.
And I lead times also shrink right.
That's because we didn't just add agents to our workflow.
We tightened the feedback loops
and we gave our agents a way to verify their own work.
And then we parallelised. Right.
We made the initial workflow as automated as possible,
but as high quality as possible. Right?
We didn't just focus on making things automated for the sake of automating them.
We made sure that we kept those review stages intact out of those guardrails,
and we made sure that the quality was consistent for that single workflow.
And then you parallelise it.
And so you noticed that even when you stop parallelising,
your quality will degrade a little bit, and you'll have to reconnect
and figure out how you can then improve that workflow even more.
So to keep that quality in check.
And so all I do all day is talk to robots.
I'm not sure when this happened, but,
yeah, hopefully that was useful for everyone.
Thank you very much.
The QR code is just, a set of links.
What was.
50% off?
No, it's just a set of links from things that I mentioned in the talk.
So if you want to go back and refer to some things, it's just yet on my website.
Yeah. Oh, do we do question there?
Yeah.
Thank you very much.
And then we can,
two questions.
First of all, since you haven't written the code in
six months, you.
Can read it.
You will be grateful for 3.2,
a different job where you actually need to write code.
And the second question is,
what's the cause of all these together?
Sorry, there's only one.
Probably not yours.
Absolutely.
So two questions.
First one is if starting code how do I keep that in practice.
And what happens when I need
to move to a job that actually needs me to write code.
And the second one is what's the costs associated.
Right.
So the first one is a very loaded question actually, because it's a question
about the way the industry is moving. Right.
If we as an industry are recognising that the productivity benefits,
again, possibly are incredibly
outweighing the costs of using coding agents,
then the chance of me moving to a job and not being allowed to use
coding agents is probably going to be pretty slim.
And if that's not the case, and if things do go crashing
and burning, and I've got to go back to writing artisanal code, then,
then it's no different to going back
and relearning something that I need to relearn.
But it's a good call out because the
the skill of writing
code is different to the skill of reviewing code.
And that's a really important call out to make.
So as you spend time doing this and reviewing a bunch of code,
know that when you go and try to write code,
you will be a lot worse at it than you were
when you were writing it regularly. So it's a really good point.
And my answer to you is I have no clue, but I think I trust myself
to figure it out enough to, deal with it.
And then the second question was about costs.
Yes, it costs a lot.
But again, if we're able to demonstrate so clearly that we are shipping
and delivering five, six, seven times as fast as we were then,
even if it costs us 1 or 2 engineers a year or,
anything in that ballpark, it's already going to be making up.
It's, it's worth.
But yeah.
That's a great.
Connection.
Okay, cool. That's a great talk. Thank you very much.
Hopefully I will not replace this in two years.
But, what I wanted to ask you is that,
I'm trying to oldest workflows right now.
Yeah.
And, I think for simple tasks, when you have,
let's say, backend necessary, then when you have a bunch of small box
that you want to fix on the surface, you can easily paralyse them.
And in this case, you got to commit or anything like that.
You just try this.
If that's true, if it works well.
But I find it's really hard to part a little less this work
when you are building a new feature that changes something fundamentally,
and you think about abstractions and how it's going to break into the system.
Or like you, if you want to blend right and you need to thoroughly
think through all of the trade offs and stuff like that, and it's just,
really hard to fertilise this kind of stuff for me.
And also, you need to review every line of code that's produced in a way.
Right?
So, what's your experience was that do you,
do you say, oh, we have the same problem or do you still verbalise it?
Because I'm always like, asking almost.
Please make sure that this code makes sense and, like, doesn't violate
any part of the sentence or, you know, it looks at the same across the board, etc..
But still some people just inquire from this is what I've parallelisation
and break.
Yes, absolutely. So
the context switching is definitely a problem.
And when you're working on a complex feature
or you're working on a task that is quite involved,
your parallelisation factor is naturally going to decrease,
and you might not be able to do as many things at once.
So it really depends on, again, it's building that muscle.
So if you're working on
a really involved feature or an involved task, you might want to pick up some small
backlog bugs that have been sitting there for like ages collecting dust.
That's one way that I found to kind of tackle this problem is that,
like if I'm working on one involved, the task that I'm working on, like 1
or 2, like small UI changes or something like completely like negligible.
That's just a time like, oh, I just haven't had time to get around to this.
But if you're working on something involved and.
Yeah, like, I don't end up parallelising as much as I would.
I think what's interesting is the stage that you're at in your company
and in your in your team, wherever it may be, impacts this the most.
If you're in an early stage.
Start-Up, the Parallelisation factor might be actually quite high
because you have to build out a bunch of different things all at the same time.
It's not that complicated
or, you know, or have a clear idea of what you want to do.
Or if you're at a really big company and everything is incredibly
well defined and structured.
So it really depends on the stage of your team, your company, and the product.
But it will vary quite a bit.
So yeah, I do face the same problem.
Cool. Yeah.
The last question would be like the next one.
So quick question because you've got some pull requests.
So how are you planning to manage complex.
So surprisingly so.
The work that I'm working on.
Not as often, because I pick and choose things
that are probably not going to conflict with each other. Right.
So if I can see the two tickets or two tasks,
I'm probably going to be touching the same code base.
I want parallelism.
Because, yeah, having to deal with a bunch of the merge conflicts,
even if you're using something like, graphite or you have stacked PRS,
it's still a pain.
So I just avoid it and come back to it when I am done with that part of the code
base for others in the team and in the company.
Dealing with merge conflicts does end up slowing down this,
and that's something that we're looking into
and trying to figure out how to, improve that part of the workflow.
And I've seen a bunch of different things where people are creating agents
that are specifically focussed on just cleaning up merge conflicts,
come up, and then fixing those things up as like in the background.
So this is yeah,
very much open to it's an open problem and an open pain point for us.
So yeah.
Round of applause for him,
Thank you.